

CONTACT

- +91 7903444694
- ✓ mddilshadbgp@gmail.com
- House No. C-48, Gali No. 5, Hari Nagar Extn., Jaitpur, Badarpur, New Delhi-110044

EDUCATION

2021 - 2023 MANUU HYDERABAD

- Master of Computer Application
- CGPA:7.61

2015 - 2018 TMBU BHAGALPUR

- Bachelor of Science in Information Technology
- Percentage: 69.13

SKILLS

- Sql Server, MySql
- WPF
- C#
- Visual Studio
- HTML, CSS
- Python
- MS Office
- Service Support

LANGUAGES

- Hindi
- English
- Urdu

MD DILSHAD

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am enthusiastic, responsible and hard working IT person. Being worked for different projects helped me to adapt to the changes quickly and made me a mature team worker. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using own initiative. I am able to work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadlines.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Integer Technology and Solutions Pvt. Ltd.
 Software Developer

2019-2021

- I have done my internship on SOFTWAE DEVELOPMENT using C# (WPF) and SQL SERVER, since 11/2019 to 04/2020..After that I working in this company as software developer for 11/2021.
- My responsibilities are designing window software using wpf, c# and sql server. I worked on many projexts like pythology management system, school management system, restaurant management system etc in this company.
- Give service support to client via phone or anydesk.

PROJECTS

- Retail Management System (WPF, C# and SQL Server)
 User can manage item, inventory and billing with ease and see many reports.
- School Management System(WPF, C# and SQL Server)
 User can manage student admission,take fee and generate result and see many reports.
- Restaurant Management System (WPF, C# and SQL Server)
 User can manage table, parcel and take away orders and see many reports.
- Pathology Management System (WPF, C# and SQL Server)
 User can manage patient details which comes from doctors and generate test result and print with doctor's header footer and see many reports.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Father's Name: Md Shamsher
 Date Of Birth: 15-08-1998
 Merital Status: Unmarried

Hobbies: Reading books, Travelling,

Watching cricket